Gökmen Görgen

gkmngrgn@gmail.com gokmengorgen.net 12557 Berlin, Germany

https://linkedin.com/in/gokmengorgen

https://github.com/gkmngrgn



ABOUT ME

I started programming by contributing to the **Pardus** project. I worked as a backend developer on the **web** for a long time. Then I developed Android **mobile** applications. I am currently working on my hobby **game** and **blockchain** projects.

SKILLS

python, rust, dart, kotlin, lisp, solidity, godot, django, android, flutter, ethereum, hyperledger

WORK EXPERIENCE

• Coachfrog AG

Oct 2015 - Present

Senior Software Engineer

Berlin, Germany

Core developer of the project sanasearch.ch from the beginning. Sanasearch is a Swiss-based search engine, booking system and online meeting platform for finding the therapists.

Radity GmbH

Jul 2012 - 2018

Co-Founder, CTO

Istanbul, Turkey

Built tech startups, created digital products, and put together tailored development teams for startups and grownups. SwissLife, Sherpany, and Coachfrog are some of the companies that I worked for.

• Markafoni

Oct 2011 - Jun 2012

Software Developer

Istanbul, Turkey

Worked in Zizigo ERP project. My first task was to send a notification mail to the customers about pending orders in Markafoni.

Artistanbul PR

Sep 2009 - Oct 2011

Software Developer

Istanbul, Turkey

Worked as a full-stack developer in a startup project named Mappiness (mappiness.com). Other projects that I developed actively are ozgurlukicin.com, idata.com.tr, no3.com.tr.

• TÜBİTAK

Aug 2009 - Oct 2009

Intern

Gebze, Kocaeli

I developed an application named Puding for installing Pardus from the USB disk. I contributed PiSi package manager and maintained XFCE desktop environment.

PROJECTS

• Tile

https://goedev.itch.io/tile

A 2D puzzle game based on drawing carpet patterns. godot, gdscript, aseprite

• Meyl

https://github.com/gkmngrgn/meyl

Static email (template) generator. rust, toml

• Blok

https://github.com/gkmngrgn/blok

A simple blockchain implementation. python, flask

• Rayt

https://github.com/gkmngrgn/rayt

Ray Tracing implementation. c++, python, rust

EDUCATION

• Management and Organization

Istanbul Arel University 2015 - 2016 Master's degree

• Economic and Administrative Sciences

Eskisehir Osmangazi University 2005 - 2010 Diploma

• High School

Tekirdağ Anatolian High School 2002 - 2005

CERTIFICATIONS

• Python (Advanced) HackerRank Sep 2020 14a74009765b • Blockchain Specialization Coursera Dec 2019 9TKPX678TZC9 • Ethereum and Solidity: The Complete Developer's Guide Udemy Dec 2019 UC-U57CMN7B • TensorFlow in Practice Specialization Coursera Nov 2019 **4VSJKATFFBGA** • Become a C++ Developer Linkedin Sep 2019 Af20iUeLVuMnsJY8CnoEnzGVxZpl • First Look: Rust Linkedin Jul 2019 ARfCpnGRdUIJ9DJg5M76Qv0w1HVV • Machine Learning: Regression Coursera Jul 2017 WWWNWHFHSJ87 Data Scientist with Python DataCamp May 2017 #60,340 Machine Learning Foundations: A Case Study Approach Coursera 48H6EDAPKS9E Apr 2017 • Functional Programming Principles in Scala Coursera Verified Certificates Dec 2014 K7HAJY444H

• Creative, Serious and Playful Science of Android Apps Coursera Verified Certificates
Feb 2014 Q9PHUHLUCZ

• Computer Science 101 Coursera
Jun 2012